<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241205190000 +0000" stop="20241205200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam, Hoss and Joe mistakenly believe their father was murdered. They split into three different directions to confront the supposed killers. In his heart, Ben knows his sons will not act outside the law; but he is not 100% sure that Joe will behave correctly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241205200000 +0000" stop="20241205203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Rebecca Snipe is returning to North Fork after a long visit away. Upon her arrival, Mark is smitten with her and gets it in his head to play matchmaker between her and his pa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241205203000 +0000" stop="20241205210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>New Orleans Menace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Tiffauges, a wealthy and sadistic Frenchman who is used to getting whatever he wants, decides he wishes to purchase the McCain Ranch. Tiffauges' lead man, Xavier, proclaims Lucas to be muy macho, and does not believe Lucas will give in so easily.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241205210000 +0000" stop="20241205220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Kitty Albright Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>"Kitty Albright is a registered nurse who's stagecoach is attacked and destroyed. Flint agrees to let her use her new skill on the wagon train. She quickly becomes disturbed at the lack of hygiene and health in general around the train."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241205220000 +0000" stop="20241205230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Promise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Responding to a vehicle fire, the firemen discover a catatonic mechanic; at Rampart the doctors are mystified by his condition. Roy lectures a woman who keeps calling the paramedics because she is lonely. A woman mixes ammonia with bleach and inhales poisonous gas. An elderly couple is trapped in their house by a bunch of tumbleweeds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241205230000 +0000" stop="20241205233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Showtime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Kaplan is to be shipped home, but becomes paranoid that something will happen to him before he leaves. He takes the wheel of the jeep to drive to Kimpo himself, but crashes and ends up in plaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241205233000 +0000" stop="20241206000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Divided We Stand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Brought on by Frank and Margaret's negative reports, General Clayton assigns a psychiatrist, Captain Hildebrand, to examine the 4077th M*A*S*H unit to see if it should be disbanded. Henry tells them to be on their best behavior, or else they will be split up. But the 4077th soon begins to act in their traditional, insane way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206000000 +0000" stop="20241206003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>5 O'clock Charlie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>An inept North Korean pilot, known as 5 O'Clock Charlie, makes his daily attempt to bomb the ammo dump. Frank puts in a request for an anti-aircraft gun, which is granted when Charlie hits General Clayton's jeep. Frank takes charge of the gun, while Hawkeye and Trapper are determined to prevent him from using it, by getting rid of the ammo dump. Frank misses Charlie and destroys the dump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206003000 +0000" stop="20241206010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Radar's Report</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar writes the weekly activity report: Hawkeye operates on a wounded prisoner who grabs a scalpel and attacks the doctors. Frank wants Klinger thrown out on a section 8, so Henry calls in a psychiatrist, Major Freedman. Hawkeye is attracted to a new nurse but thinks she is married. Trapper loses a patient who developed complications during the O.R. fracas with the wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206010000 +0000" stop="20241206013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee The Crusader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee and most of the women in town rally against Andy when he tries to evict a much-beloved butter and egg man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206013000 +0000" stop="20241206020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Sidecar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney comes back from a police auction with a motorcycle and sidecar. After he upsets the whole town with the conveyance, Andy has to find a way to convince Barney to give up the bike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206020000 +0000" stop="20241206023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampett-hewes Empire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed and Howard Hewes are preparing to get their airport deal all wrapped up, and Drysdale decides to come visit the famous recluse of a billionaire. He brings along Jane, who is dressed in jeans and an old sweatshirt to look like she has the simple touch, and his three secretaries to sing "Howard Hughes, We Love You."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206023000 +0000" stop="20241206030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Arnold Ziffel, Boy Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Arnold is opening an account at the Pixley Bank when two robbers make off with a bundle of cash and the pig's five dollars. The pair hides out at the Douglases' farm, taking Lisa, Oliver and Eb hostage. Arnold makes off with their bag of money and takes it to the authorities while the clueless criminals force Lisa to make hotcakes for them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206030000 +0000" stop="20241206033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Birthday, Dear Hogan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan's men plan to surprise him for his birthday by blowing up an ammunition dump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206033000 +0000" stop="20241206040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Forget To Write</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink fails a physical and gets combat duty at the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206040000 +0000" stop="20241206043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Berry And Eydie Gorme</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Carol and Vicki disturb Harvey while he attempts to finish his taxes. Then, in Salute to RKO Studio, the gang parodies classic films, including "The Pride of the Yankees", "Notorious", "The Outlaw", and "Quasimodo".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206043000 +0000" stop="20241206053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Runaway Corpse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed Davenport fears that his wife is trying to poison him. Later, Davenport falls ill and blames her from his deathbed. After he dies, his body disappears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206053500 +0000" stop="20241206060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Whole Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A peculiar Model A automobile compels a used car dealer to tell only the truth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206060500 +0000" stop="20241206063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Never Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Karen has a problem with alcohol, one that leaves her wondering what happened the previous night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206063500 +0000" stop="20241206070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Gentlemen From America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Howard Latimer accepts a peculiar bet: to spend the night at a supposedly haunted manor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206070500 +0000" stop="20241206080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Portrait Of A Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix investigates the mysterious death of an Air Force pilot who died right before the presentation of an experimental aircraft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206080500 +0000" stop="20241206090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Lonely Place To Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A syndicate boss may just be next in line to be murdered when Cannon investigates a case involving a triple homicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206090500 +0000" stop="20241206100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Sanctuary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A rapist terrorizes a resort where Betty is vacationing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206100000 +0000" stop="20241206103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Released Convert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A patient parolee decides the time is finally right to attempt the recovery of stolen money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206103000 +0000" stop="20241206110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A gang of juvenile thieves have been stealing petty items in order to gain membership into an exclusive club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206110000 +0000" stop="20241206113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Southwest Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While responding to a baseless complaint against an elderly artist, Malloy decides to buy a random painting out of pity and makes Reed envious. Meanwhile, they question a man attempting to break into a gumball machine while his son looks on, get a big surprise after tracking down a suspected peeping tom, deal with a man who comes up with a creative way to avoid having his furniture repossessed and engage in a game of cat-and-mouse inside the Los Angeles Coliseum with a former football player turned suspected robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206113000 +0000" stop="20241206120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Sweet Smell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A clumsy elderly woman spills a large bottle of perfume in Malloy and Reed's patrol car, resulting in a most unpleasant work day. Meanwhile, a reported burglar in a church office results in a comical case of mistaken identity, a well-meaning man is accused of kidnapping his granddaughter and a young boy asks for help locating his stolen bicycle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206120000 +0000" stop="20241206130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Snowbirds</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony escape the winter and head to sunny Florida for some warm adventures."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206130000 +0000" stop="20241206133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Cat Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A strange cat appears at the Cleaver's door and Beaver takes it in and feeds it. However, when the owner is found, and the cat is returned, Beaver finds himself with a dilemma: The cat keeps coming back!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206133000 +0000" stop="20241206140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Weekend Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally gets a job at the ice cream parlor leaving a gaggle of girls swooning and Eddie and Lumpy feeling neglected. So to get back at him, Eddie and Lumpy concoct a plan of revenge that involves Mary Ellen Roger's slumber party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206140000 +0000" stop="20241206150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Provocative Protégé</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Washed up pianist David Carpenter is knocked out and pushed over a cliff for insurance money. Carpenter's beautiful protege, Donna Ross, immediately comes under suspicion by the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206150000 +0000" stop="20241206160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Lemon  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock's new neighbor, Les "Ace" Calhoun (Don Knotts), is charged with murdering the used car salesman who sold him a lemon, Matlock takes the case to prove that more than one person had a motive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206160000 +0000" stop="20241206170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>An Occupational Hazard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A secretary takes drastic measures to protect herself from sexual harassment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206170000 +0000" stop="20241206180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Outsider</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben surprises his family by bringing home a woman - his new bride</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206180000 +0000" stop="20241206190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Predators</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A former gunfighter returns to Dodge, which worries Matt because Howard Cane survived the rage war. Can Matt stop him before more trouble comes to Dodge?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206190000 +0000" stop="20241206200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Hoss And The Leprechauns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss goes leprechaun hunting, hoping to find gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206200000 +0000" stop="20241206203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Apprentice Sheriff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Willard is filling in as temporary marshal while Micah is away. Some Texas cowhands are in North Fork looking for some fun and relaxation, but Dan keeps coming down hard on them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206203000 +0000" stop="20241206210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Angry Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark, returning from selling their herd, share the stagecoach trip with a Marshal and his prisoner, Johnny Cotton. Johnny's gang arrives to free their partner and steal the contents of the stage's strongbox, as well as Lucas' money and rifle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206210000 +0000" stop="20241206220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Maud Frazer Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>"Maud Frazer takes command of her wagon train after all the men are killed. Flint tries to dissuade Maud from going through hostile Indian country where there is gold.. She proceeds anyway but is forced to change plans."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206220000 +0000" stop="20241206230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Body Language</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A crop-duster makes a rough landing in a field; the pilot suffers a punctured lung, and a bystander is poisoned with pesticide. A patient reports to Rampart with an ear infection caused by mothballs. A couple overdoses on daffodil bulbs. A weekend cowboy refuses treatment after falling from his horse. Two victims of a traffic accident get friendly. The lead singer of a rock band goes into cardiac arrest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206230000 +0000" stop="20241206233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For The Good Of The Outfit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper want the army to admit responsibility for the accidental bombing of a local village. They fill out a report and Major Stoner arrives to investigate, and leaves with all the evidence. When the story is released it claims that the enemy bombed the village, and the army tries to gag the doctors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241206233000 +0000" stop="20241207000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Pierce And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye has been in non-stop surgery for three straight days without sleep, and the wounded keep coming. He decides to find out who started the war, and sends a telegram to Harry S Truman. After listening to some of Frank's rubbish about the North Koreans wanting better plumbing, he tries to send the officers' latrine to the North Koreans with an offer of peace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207000000 +0000" stop="20241207003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Kim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye operates on a five-year-old Korean boy, and Radar can't find his family. Henry plans to send him to the orphanage, and the camp enjoys his company while they can. Trapper decides to adopt him after consulting his wife, and has to rescue him after he wanders into the minefield.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207003000 +0000" stop="20241207010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>L.i.p.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Corporal Walker is being sent home, and he wants to marry his Korean girl so she and their baby can return with him. CID sends Lt Willis to investigate, but when he refuses Hawkeye and Trapper frame him. Hawkeye is upset that a nurse he was pursuing does not approve of the marriage between "a gook" and "one of us."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207010000 +0000" stop="20241207013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>My Fair Ernest T. Bass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy tries to make a silk purse out of a sow's ear when he takes it upon himself to turn Ernest T. into a presentable gentleman. The big test comes at Mrs. Wiley's weekly reception, at which Andy passes him off as his cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207013000 +0000" stop="20241207020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Prisoner Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lady prisoner woos Andy and Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207020000 +0000" stop="20241207023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>What Happened To Shorty?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Shad Heller visits the Clampetts, Jed asks what happened to Shorty Kellems, but Shad doesn't know. Meanwhile, the Clampetts are having food stolen from the root cellar. They decide to investigate during the night and catch Shorty in the kitchen having a snack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207023000 +0000" stop="20241207030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Flight To Nowhere</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The farmers of Hooterville sign up for a government-sponsored agriculture exchange program to Europe. When they realize the $300 cost for tickets is per person, not per plane-load, they decide to supply their own airplane with Oliver as their pilot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207030000 +0000" stop="20241207033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan steals a Luftwaffe codebook, but must organize a special mission when Newkirk drops it down a well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207033000 +0000" stop="20241207040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Klink Commandos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men volunteer for a German suicide squad train bound for the Russian front in order to steal key documents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207040000 +0000" stop="20241207043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests David Hartman And Paula Kelly</sub-title>
    <desc>In Nora Desmond, Carol plays a washed-up, silent film actress who goes to dinner for the first time in years. Then, in George and Zelda, Carol questions a doctor's methods to treat her sick husband. Finally, in This Is Your Lifetime, a parody of "This Is Your Life", Carol is embarrassed  when she's caught on camera at the gym after gaining weight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207043000 +0000" stop="20241207053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crooked Candle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>While Martha Bradford is waiting for her appointment at a beauty parlor, she meets Rita Bradford, who apparently also is married to her husband and lives at the same address. Soon, Mr. Bradford turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207053500 +0000" stop="20241207060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Invaders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>An old woman in an isolated farmhouse is troubled by the appearance of tiny aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207060500 +0000" stop="20241207063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Sitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Lottie Slocum is excited to be the center of attention after the woman she babysits for is murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207063500 +0000" stop="20241207070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Belfry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A jealous man kills the fiancé of his unrequited love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207070500 +0000" stop="20241207080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Inside Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Traveling to New Orleans, Mannix goes undercover in the Big Easy to protect an informer and avenge the death of a pal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207080500 +0000" stop="20241207090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>No Pockets In A Shroud</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When an heir of a millionaire who prefers to live like a hermit is discovered to be missing, Cannon in hired to investigate and uncovers a mysterious case of murder and embezzlement. But the case is hampered by the hermit's attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207090500 +0000" stop="20241207100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Dive, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Treasure hunters falsify the facts of a diver's death to prevent anyone from meddling in their quest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207100000 +0000" stop="20241207103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Camping Trip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobbie Jo invites her new boyfriend, Orrin, along on a family camping trip, much to the chagrin of Uncle Joe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207103000 +0000" stop="20241207110000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Day At Shady Rest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E26</episode-num>
    <desc>"Deputy" Joe Carson captures a desperate bank robber with the help of Aunt Helen and a war-surplus life raft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207110000 +0000" stop="20241207113000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Possum Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale tries to keep the Clampetts in Beverly Hills by telling them there is going to be a Possum Day held there. Granny decides to run for Possum Queen in Beverly Hills, and Drysdale convinces her that she is running against Mrs. Drysdale. Meanwhile, Drysdale is desperate to actually get a Possum Day to happen for the Clampetts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207113000 +0000" stop="20241207120000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Possum Day Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is preparing for her Possum Queen campaign, and also wondering why Mrs. Drysdale hasn’t fought back yet. When Jed asks Drysdale about this, he starts her campaign with a false radio interview and continues to try to get a Possum festival going. Granny continues with her campaign, and Mrs. Drysdale realizes that she has been campaigning without even knowing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207120000 +0000" stop="20241207123000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Kickin’ The Congo Round, Little Swee’pea, The Anvil Chorus Girl</sub-title>
    <desc>"Sailors Popeye and his rival Bluto are in a Latin American port, vying with each other for the attentions of Olivia Oylia, a conga-loving woman., Popeye tackles lions, bears, snakes and countless other animals chasing after Swee'pea at the zoo only to find himself the victim of an assault by Olive for scaring Swee'pea with a toy on their arrival home., Popeye and Bluto pass by Olive's blacksmith shop and are smitten."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207123000 +0000" stop="20241207130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Filet-meow, Alias St. Nick, Cannery Rodent</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jerry rescues a fish from Tom and when Tom tries to bring the fish back he finds a shark instead., A cat, dressed up as Santa Claus, tries to fool Mrs. Mouse and her family of mice on Christmas Eve but Little Cheeser doesn't believe in St. Nick and has doubts about the imposter., Tom and Jerry get trapped inside a can in Cannery Row."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207130000 +0000" stop="20241207140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Box Car Bandit, Rough And Tumbleweed, Fish Hooked, Hypnotic Hick, Knock Knock, Kittens' Mittens, Nautical Nut</sub-title>
    <desc>"A bandit and his horse attempt to rob a train guarded by Woody., Inspector Willoughby pursues a Wild West outlaw., Chilly eats fish at an aquarium where Smedley is working., After being offered a reward, Woody hypnotizes Buzz into answering a summons from a law officer., Andy and Papa try to stop Woody from pecking on their roof., Three kittens blame their lost mittens on a vagabond cat, who will bear the punishment if they don't tell the truth., Woody is mistakenly captured and brought aboard a ship, where he pranks the captain and first mate."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207140000 +0000" stop="20241207150000 +0000">
    <title>A Very Merry Bugs Bunny Christmas</title>
    <sub-title>Bugs Bunny's Christmas Carol, Gift Wrapped, Abominable Snow Rabbit, Freeze Frame, Weasel While You Work, The Fright Before Christmas</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Sam lacks the Christmas spirit, Bugs Bunny makes a plan to change his mind., It's Christmas time and Sylvester tries to switch his present with Granny's present which is Tweety in a birdcage., Bugs and Daffy decide to tunnel underground over to Palm Springs. Wrong directions end them up in the Himalayas where they run into trouble with the Abominable Snowman... , The coyote orders a blizzard machine to cover the entire desert with snow after he finds out that Road Runners are easy to catch in the cold. , During a snow-covered winter, Foghorn Leghorn uses the weasel against the barn's guard dog. , Taz breaks free of his a plane shipping crate and falls from the sky into Santa's laundry. He hijacks Santa's sleigh and ends up in Bugs' house tearing down everything, but Bugs gets wise to the Devil. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207150000 +0000" stop="20241207160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Whirring Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Loveless plans on making California a kingdom for children.... using exploding toys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207160000 +0000" stop="20241207170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The St. Nicholas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>As Christmas Eve approaches, the wagon train encounters a happy time, the perils that go with hostile indians and a little lost boy who may have already been captured by those same hostiles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207170000 +0000" stop="20241207180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Judgement In Heaven</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Jarrod risks inviting his client home for a Christmas visit. She's a young woman accused of aiding and abetting her boyfriend, an outlaw who has recently escaped from jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207180000 +0000" stop="20241207190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>P.s. Murry Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The meanest outlady in the U.S. is coming to Dodge, at least that's what Festus has heard. In actuality, it's Emma Grundy out to retrieve her seven orphans from Titus Spangler and take them back to the orphanage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207190000 +0000" stop="20241207200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young singer agrees to perform at Virginia City's annual orphan's Christmas benefit, his shifty manager demands a cut of the donations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207200000 +0000" stop="20241207203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Young Englishman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas gets in trouble when he accuses the foreman of a neighboring ranch of rustling some of his cattle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207203000 +0000" stop="20241207210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Gaucho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Rumson, without even saying to whom he had sold his property, left the bill of sale with the bank and moved away from North Fork. Curge, who's highest offer was upped by $1,000, is upset because Rumson sold out to a "peppergut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207210000 +0000" stop="20241207220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Twenty-five Santa Clauses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A conman and his wife con the drovers into pooling their efforts to prepare a Christmas celebration for a sickly Mexican boy. The boy isn't really sick and Rowdy ignores Favor's orders to move the herd across a river, trapping the herd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207220000 +0000" stop="20241207223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Be Not Forgetful Of Strangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Duane Eddy as a cowboy who arrives in town during Christmas with his pregnant wife---and no lodgings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207223000 +0000" stop="20241207230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Eight Cent Reward</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>On Christmas Eve Randall receives his most daunting assignment yet: bring in Santa Claus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241207230000 +0000" stop="20241208010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Slippery Silks, Dizzy Doctors, Calling All Curs, Dunked In The Deep, He Cooked His Goose, Spooks</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are carpenters who inherit a fancy dress boutique.   , Larry, Curly and Moe make a grand mess of things when they mistake the medicine they're selling for auto polish.  , The stooges are private detectives hired to find a missing girl, which leads to a mad scientist. , Veternarians Moe, Curly and Larry find their business going to the dogs when one of their prize patients is stolen and held for ransom. , The Stooges are tricked into becoming stowaways by their neighbor "Borscht", a spy for an enemy country.  Stranded on a freighter on the high seas, they discover that their friend has concealed some stolen microfilm in watermelons they brought aboard for him.  After a wild chase, they subdue Borscht and recover the microfilm. , Larry is a pet dealer who's seeing Moe's wife while at the same time trying to steal Shemp's fiancee.  When Moe's become suspicious, Larry attempts to frame Shemp as the boyfriend.  He gets Shemp a job as a door-to-door pajama salesman and sends him to Moe's apartment, and then tells both Moe and Shemp's fiancee to go there and catch him in the act.  Larry's plan backfires when Shemp catches him and lets Moe deliver some punishment. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208010000 +0000" stop="20241208033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Comedy Of Terrors</sub-title>
    <desc>"A horror spoof in which a funeral director, who is in arrears on his rent, aggressively pursues customers to bolster his business--and the fact that they haven't died yet doesn't seem to dissuade him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208033000 +0000" stop="20241208040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Batman Is Riled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Joker switches utility belts with Batman as they track him down in his lair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208040000 +0000" stop="20241208050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>And The Children Shall Lead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise travels to a planet where a scientific team has killed themselves. All that is left alive are the children, and they soon begin to act oddly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208050000 +0000" stop="20241208060000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Zombie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A grandmother seeks revenge for her grandson's death by turning him into a zombie to do her bidding.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208060000 +0000" stop="20241208070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Return From Outer Space</sub-title>
    <desc>"Nobody believes Will Robinson when he sends himself back to Earth with an alien transporter, since the world believes they all had died once they realized their ship had gone off course. Lost in Space's only Christmas program."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208070000 +0000" stop="20241208080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Long Live The King</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Admiral Nelson must get a 12-year-old prince back to his country to assume the throne before the reds take over.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208080000 +0000" stop="20241208090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of Thrombeldinbar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Fitzhuge pretends to be a magical holiday elf to entertain two orphan children. But the ruse turns deadly when he discovers that the giants ritually throw Thrombeldinbar into a fire to celebrate the holiday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208090000 +0000" stop="20241208100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Massacre</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The time travelers try to save themselves from the massacre of Custer's Seventh Cavalry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208100000 +0000" stop="20241208110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Task Force</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent and the believers meet with a publishing magnate</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208110000 +0000" stop="20241208120000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Powers Of Matthew Star</sub-title>
    <desc>"After developing powers, a teenager realizes he's not from Earth."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208120000 +0000" stop="20241208123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Up Is Hard To Undo   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>First, it's splitsville for Zack and Kelly when Kelly goes on a date with her ex-boyfriend. Slater and Jessie are finally a couple, but things get messed up when they disagree on how to celebrate their coupledom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208123000 +0000" stop="20241208130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Video Yearbook   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack and the gang decide to make a video yearbook for Bayside, but when Zack uses the opportunity to create the "Girls of Bayside Dating Service," his friends get him back big time!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208130000 +0000" stop="20241208133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Snow White And The Seven Dorks   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang puts together a hip-hop version of 'Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs,' and Zack and Jessie get caught in a serious situation when Lisa catches them rehearsing the final scene—the KISS!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208133000 +0000" stop="20241208140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Dance (part 1)   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Kelly gets a job working at The Max but may have to tell Zack it's over between them when she falls for her boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208140000 +0000" stop="20241208143000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Aftermath (part 2)   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack seeks revenge after catching Kelly with Jeff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208143000 +0000" stop="20241208150000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Fake Ids   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Zack falls for a college girl, he lies about his age and makes fake IDs so he, Slater and Screech can sneak into an 18-and-over dance club. While there, they see Kelly's boyfriend dancing with another girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208150000 +0000" stop="20241208153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Voice Of Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Carol is asked to sing at church on Christmas, but loses her voice just days before the event. A hopeful Cindy asks a department store Santa Claus to bring Carol's voice back in time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208153000 +0000" stop="20241208160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Father Of The Year</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcia enters Mike in a "Father of the Year" contest through the newspaper, but in order to mail her entry before the deadline she breaks curfew. Mike catches her but she's unable to explain, and he grounds her from the family ski trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208160000 +0000" stop="20241208163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Fonzie receives a Christmas gift from his father but is reluctant to accept and open it. Meanwhile, Richie and Lori Beth argue about what they've spent on each other's gifts, and Joanie is upset at Howard for getting an artificial tree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208163000 +0000" stop="20241208170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Oh, Come All Ye Bums</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The gang works to raise money for Frank's annual hobo Christmas dinner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208170000 +0000" stop="20241208173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Otis has Mayberry worried when he buys a car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208173000 +0000" stop="20241208180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy And John Wayne</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy is spotted while attempting to "collect" a cement block with John Wayne's footprints from Grauman's Chinese Theater. To avoid publicity and keep Lucy out of jail, Ricky enlists John Wayne's help in replacing the block. One mishap leads to another, and the plot thickens—as does the cement. John Wayne guest-stars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208180000 +0000" stop="20241208183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Takes A Drive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Beaver and Gilbert are pretending to go for a drive in Ward's car, Beaver accidentally releases the parking brake, causing the car to roll down the driveway and into the street, backing up traffic. Wally steps in and drives the car back in the driveway and clears up the traffic mess, but he soon finds himself being issued a citation for driving without a license.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208183000 +0000" stop="20241208190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Big Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's school is having an exchange dance and Wally and Eddie must take girls from a rival school that they chose out of a hat. Eddie asks to trade with Wally and he agrees, like a shot, after seeing the picture of Eddie's intended in a yearbook. Suspicious, Wally soon quickly discovers why Eddie wanted to trade; the girl is a few inches taller than Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208190000 +0000" stop="20241208193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Home For Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts decide to head home for Christmas, and once Drysdale and Jane hear about this, they make all the arrangements, getting Granny and Elly mink coats and giving the Clampetts their first plane ride in style. After a slight mix-up, the Clampetts finally get home, surprising Pearl and Jethrine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208193000 +0000" stop="20241208200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>No Place Like Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts arrive back at their old cabin to spend the Christmas holiday with Pearl. But since the cabin will be too crowded with the Clampetts and Brewster, Pearl suggests Brewster stays with her, in an attempt to get engaged. She tries to woo Brewster by showing herself off at the theatre she works at during the premiere of 'Ben Hur.'</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208200000 +0000" stop="20241208203000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Birds Gotta Fly, Fish Gotta Talk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>During Christmas, the castaways get homesick and recall the day they were shipwrecked.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208203000 +0000" stop="20241208210000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Gilligan Goes Gung-ho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan is made a deputy sheriff, and begins to take his job too seriously.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208210000 +0000" stop="20241208213000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Santa Mama  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama fills in for Vint as a mall Santa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208213000 +0000" stop="20241208220000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Gets Goosed  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama's cousin gives the Harpers a live goose for Christmas dinner, Mama relives memories of her childhood while the rest of the family is horrified at the thought of killing their new pet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208220000 +0000" stop="20241208230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Lonely At The Top</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>In a Christmas-themed cruise, a group of orphans and a man convicted for a crime he didn't commit are among those aboard the ship. Florence Henderson, Donna Mills and Shecky Greene guest star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208230000 +0000" stop="20241208233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A modern-day Scrooge (businessman Ben Weaver) causes trouble on Christmas Eve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241208233000 +0000" stop="20241209000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Video Games- Linda Guillory</sub-title>
    <desc>"You might say Linda Guillory is hooked on video games. Obsessed with them as a kid, Linda played and usually beat everyone she competed against. As an adult,she found and bought all of her childhood games and then added some more, for good measure. She currently holds 2 Guiness Word Records for her voulminous vintage video game collection, and even became an engineer so she could figure out how they work. Linda's collection  began with her Coleco Pacman, but she is no less passionate about Zelda and her entire set of Mattel handheld games. Linda's sister Cynthia joins us today and can attest to how competitive her sister is, while our expert, Scott, who's made a career out of video games will be forced to evaluate her entire collection, and then see if he can come up with a video game she doesn't already have so that they can possibly make a trade. Good luck with that, Scott!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209000000 +0000" stop="20241209003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye writes home, describing Christmas in Korea: Radar ships a jeep home, a piece at a time; Henry gives the monthly lecture on sex, with the aid of figure A and figure B; Trapper helps deliver a calf; Klinger and Frank get into a fight, but Father Mulcahy smoothes things over; Hawkeye and Trapper sabotage Margaret's tent; Hawkeye flies to the front line dressed as Santa to help a wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209003000 +0000" stop="20241209010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy writes a pre-Christmas letter to his sister, who is a nun. He recounts his frustrations at not being more effective at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209010000 +0000" stop="20241209013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Day At The Bunker's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Christmas Day and Archie is the only one not in the Christmas spirit. Mike and Gloria question him, but he refuses to reveal what's bugging him. The Jeffersons come over to wish the Bunkers a "Merry Christmas", but this does anything but cheer Archie up especially since Henry is dressed as Santa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209013000 +0000" stop="20241209020000 +0000">
    <title>Good Times</title>
    <sub-title>Penny's Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Christmas season has the Evans family in the spirit and planning a Christmas Eve party. Meanwhile, while Christmas shopping for her mother, Penny gets her wallet stolen, and later steals a necklace from a department store in a desperate attempt to try</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209020000 +0000" stop="20241209023000 +0000">
    <title>Good Times</title>
    <sub-title>The Traveling Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Keith's Scrooge-like boss at the taxi-cab company won't give him Christmas off, the Evans family brings their Christmas party to Keith and holds at the company. J.J. hosts the festivities and it features Michael singing, Bookman (dressed as Santa) da</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209023000 +0000" stop="20241209030000 +0000">
    <title>Sanford and Son</title>
    <sub-title>Ebenezer Sanford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Fred is a Scrooge-like miser during the Christmas season and his friends try to get him to join into the Christmas spirit, but he rejects the attempts. After being accused of a being a Scrooge, Fred falls asleep and dreams up "A Christmas Carol." Now it i</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209030000 +0000" stop="20241209033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Betty White</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Mama cleans out the attic, and Eunice finds out what happened to her childhood bunny. Then, in Counterfeit Bill, Carol tries to get rid of a fake twenty dollar bill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209033000 +0000" stop="20241209040000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Alan Alda</sub-title>
    <desc>In Nobody Does It Like Me, a department store Santa and a toy department wrapper sing after the store has closed. Then, in The Family, Eunice's brother visits, but every time he tries to speak, they cut him off with their problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209040000 +0000" stop="20241209043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Alan Brady Show Presents</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>"The Alan Brady Show" performs their Christmas variety show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209043000 +0000" stop="20241209050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Brave And The Backache</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura wonders why Rob never wants to be alone with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209050000 +0000" stop="20241209053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>On Stage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, Alice and Ed are in a Raccoon play, and Ralph expects to be a big star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209053000 +0000" stop="20241209060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Penny For Your Thoughts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Gaining telepathic abilities when his coin lands on its edge, a mild-mannered bank clerk learns about the difference between other people's plans and fantasies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209060000 +0000" stop="20241209070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>I Saw The Whole Thing  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A well-known mystery author is accused of running a stop sign before hitting a motorcyclist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209070000 +0000" stop="20241209080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Where The Action Is</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>While working as a hotel lifeguard in Reno, Nevada, Kimble is caught in the middle of a feud between the hotel owner Dan Polichek, and his spoiled and rambunctious teenage daughter Christine. 'Chris' believes her father drove away her mother whom committe</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209080000 +0000" stop="20241209090000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Double Circle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Art collector Victor Laszlo and his partner, Dunson, have stolen a new fuel formula from the U.S. and killed the one scientist capable of duplicating the formula. The IMF must recover the formula from Laszlo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209090000 +0000" stop="20241209093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Motorcycle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A grudge leads to the accidental death of a Highway Patrol officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209093000 +0000" stop="20241209100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A dead man has been found in a locked room, along with a gun that could not have been the murder weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209100000 +0000" stop="20241209103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Grenade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A surly teenager throws acid on the back of another student and later crashes a party armed with a live hand grenade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209103000 +0000" stop="20241209110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Shooting Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday lands in hot water after a thief he attempted to apprehend, and in the process shot at, turns up dead and SID can't find evidence that the man fired at Friday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209110000 +0000" stop="20241209113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Trouble In The Bank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>While on a quiet patrol, Reed decides to spend part of his lunch break doing business at his bank while Malloy waits in the patrol car. Unfortunately, he walks into the clutches of a pair of ruthless robbers who take him hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209113000 +0000" stop="20241209120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>North Hollywood Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed volunteers to write a profile on Malloy for the LAPD's magazine to honor his 10th anniversary on the force, but soon discovers he may be in over his head. Out on patrol, an apparent gas station armed robbery gets turned on its head when they question the parties after a long chase, a man goes to extreme lengths to get his neighbor's poodle to stop barking, a woman's plan to get her husband arrested backfires and a liquor store robbery suspect barricades himself inside a house's garage after a high-speed chase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209120000 +0000" stop="20241209130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Rock-a-billy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony dive into all things rockabilly! Special guest Jeff Cole of the Rockabilly Artists Alliance joins."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209130000 +0000" stop="20241209133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Ice Skates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver wants a new pair of expensive ice skates and asks Ward to borrow $13. Wanting to pick them out himself, he goes to the store and is conned by a salesman who sells him skates that are three sizes too big.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209133000 +0000" stop="20241209140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Weekend Invitation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and a bunch of other guys are invited to spend the weekend at Scott's cottage on the lake. However, Scott doesn't mention to Wally that there will be no parent supervision.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209140000 +0000" stop="20241209150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Nine Dolls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason's fishing trip to Scotland is interrupted by seven-year-old Peggy Smith. Peggy is living at a boarding school and searching for her real parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209150000 +0000" stop="20241209160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Informer: Part 1  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Sam Chandler is found murdered, his lawyer, David O'Malley, is the prime suspect—in part because Sam was sleeping with David's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209160000 +0000" stop="20241209170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Last Rights</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil fears for his Aunt Ruda's safety after several killings occur in the hospital where she is being treated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209170000 +0000" stop="20241209180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Torch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>An old girlfriend of John Walton buys the Drew Drop Inn where Jason works.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209180000 +0000" stop="20241209190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Yankton</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A drifter wants to marry a rich family's daughter</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209190000 +0000" stop="20241209200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Prime Of Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben Cartwright doubts his fitness to run the Ponderosa when his impatience results in a logging camp accident that causes serious injury to himself and an old friend's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209200000 +0000" stop="20241209203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Pet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward Haskins guns down Joe Flecker, who has evidence that could be used to blackmail him. Haskins thinks the information was given to Lucas because he brought Flecker to the doctor before he died. Stirred up by Haskins behavior, Lucas goes through Flecker's things, finding a wanted poster for Haskins in the sole of Flecker's boot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209203000 +0000" stop="20241209210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sheridan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Blandon, a man with only one good arm, wanders onto the ranch. Lucas gives Blandon a job to "hire him and Mark a clear conscience." General Sheridan and his patrol wander by and Lucas offers to let them stay the night at the ranch. Blandon once pulled a gun on General Sheridan; as it turns out, Blandon was a Confederate soldier who once had General Sheridan in his gun sight during the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209210000 +0000" stop="20241209220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Selena Hartnell Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>"Selena Hartnell joins the train after bandits attack her wagon. Later, she reveals she is a bounty hunter looking for William Barrett, a murderer on the run. It turns out that Barrett is Will Cottrell, the leader of pacifists on the train."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209220000 +0000" stop="20241209230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Understanding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>At an explosive fire, a girl's horse is trapped in a burning barn. Dr. Brackett and Nurse McCall lecture a man who keeps forgetting his insulin shots. A girl calls the hospital, threatening suicide; firemen stand by while hospital workers attempt to trace the call. A hostage in a bank robbery has heart problems; the paramedics must treat him at gunpoint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209230000 +0000" stop="20241209233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial Of Henry Blake</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Majors Houlihan and Burns press charges against Colonel Blake to get him arrested and put Frank in charge. They also put Hawkeye and Trapper under arrest so that they can't help Henry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241209233000 +0000" stop="20241210000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad... Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Once more Hawkeye writes home to his father: the doctors operate on a soldier with a grenade shot into his body; Hawkeye and Trapper color the skin of a racist patient, who demanded the right color blood, while he is asleep; Henry gets a movie of his daughter's birthday from home; the officers hold the monthly staff meeting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210000000 +0000" stop="20241210003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Sniper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A lone sniper has the 4077th pinned down—including Radar and Henry in the shower. The poor boy thinks he's firing on McArthur's headquarters, and a chopper finally comes by and wounds him with gunfire from above, ending the siege. Hawkeye walks out to into the bush to tend to the wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210003000 +0000" stop="20241210010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Carry On Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp succumbs to the Asian flu, except for Hawkeye and Margaret, who have to do everything themselves. As the others start to recover, Hawkeye falls ill but he still manages to operate when wounded arrive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210010000 +0000" stop="20241210013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Song Festers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer's singing voice surprises everyone, especially Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210013000 +0000" stop="20241210020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Shoplifters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Weaver's Department store is being robbed, presumably by shoplifters. Barney poses as a mannequin to catch a thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210020000 +0000" stop="20241210023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>To keep Shorty in line, Shad has built a cage. Shorty escapes but is soon captured and brought to his wedding rehearsal. The slippery Shorty, however, escapes again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210023000 +0000" stop="20241210030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>My Mother The Countess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On learning that Lisa's mother is coming for a visit, the Hooterville residents go overboard in wanting to welcome the countess. Despite Oliver's protests that she's not royalty, they forge ahead anyway with plans for a parade and marching band.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210030000 +0000" stop="20241210033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gasoline War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men plan to destroy a gasoline station that has just been built in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210033000 +0000" stop="20241210040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Unfair Exchange</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan kidnaps Burkhalter's sister in order to exchange her for a captured Allied agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210040000 +0000" stop="20241210043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests William Conrad And Isabel Sanford</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Harvey mistakenly steals another man's wallet. Then, in TV Blackouts, the gang salutes TV shows, including "Sonny and Cher, "Jack LaLanne", "Password", "The Golddiggers", and "Maude".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210043000 +0000" stop="20241210053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Negligent Nymph</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason and Paul Drake are on a fishing trip when they spot a young woman being pursued by vicious guard dogs on an island estate. After the two men pull her from the ocean, it is discovered that in her possession is a note intended for her employer, accusing him of killing his rich uncle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210053500 +0000" stop="20241210060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Twenty-two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>While in the hospital recovering from overwork, a woman keeps dreaming about room 22, the hospital morgue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210060500 +0000" stop="20241210063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Hidden Thing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Dana needs to find the license plate number of the car that killed his fiancée.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210063500 +0000" stop="20241210070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A prince sets his eye on Irene and her money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210070500 +0000" stop="20241210080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Kill A Memory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to uncover the past life of an amnesia victim who is a Vietnam veteran.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210080500 +0000" stop="20241210090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Stone Cold Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The reopening of the cold case of a salesgirl reveals that a bicycle she sold may be a clue to her death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210090500 +0000" stop="20241210100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Nest Of Scorpions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>J.R. goes to a mountain resort to find real estate developer who's gone missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210100000 +0000" stop="20241210103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Mental Patient</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>An escapee from a mental hospital is the primary suspect in the violent death of a farmer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210103000 +0000" stop="20241210110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Badge Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Three con artists have been swindling businessmen from out of town by posing as a prostitute and two policemen. The detectives set a trap as Gannon pretends to be a manufacturer from Lincoln, Nebraska.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210110000 +0000" stop="20241210113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Taking It Easy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed gets stuck manning the front desk after spraining his wrist, where he must deal with a caller who claims to have planted a bomb at the station, a young man who wants to file a claim of police brutality and an elderly man who walks in with a shotgun. Meanwhile, Malloy is assigned a partner who is a first-day rookie, and they deal with three young children from Oklahoma who are abandoned by their mother, and engage in a high-speed pursuit that ends in a most unexpected way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210113000 +0000" stop="20241210120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Krash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy's brand new car gets dinged up when he has to bail out to chase down a purse snatcher, but Sgt. MacDonald promises him his kid brother in Beverly Hills can fix it on the cheap. Out on patrol, he and Reed search for a drunk man accused of randomly shooting arrows, respond to a robbery at a deli that results in tragedy and search for a drug store robbery suspect who gets away after being shot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210120000 +0000" stop="20241210130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Historic Feuds</sub-title>
    <desc>"From royal rule to fictional families, Bill and Toony tackle legendary rivalries!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210130000 +0000" stop="20241210133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's English Test</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has been having trouble in English and Ward persuades Wally to tutor him. Wally has Beaver look over an old exam that he once took. To Beaver's surprise, the next day his teacher gives him the exact same test, which, of course, he aces. However, Beaver is left with a guilty conscience.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210133000 +0000" stop="20241210140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Chauffeur</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally plans on going to a big dance with Evelyn Boothby and they plan on getting there cramped with six other people in Lumpy's car. When June and Ward refuse to allow that, Wally and Evelyn must find another way to get there. However, what Evelyn has in mind doesn't go over well with Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210140000 +0000" stop="20241210150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Loquacious Liar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lester Martin's life takes a horrible turn for the worse when a man breaks into his apartment, forces him at gun-point to drink half a bottle of Scotch and then drives him into the country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210150000 +0000" stop="20241210160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Informer: Part 2  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Sam Chandler is found murdered, his lawyer, David O'Malley, is the prime suspect—in part because Sam was sleeping with David's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210160000 +0000" stop="20241210170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>When The Music Stopped</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Singer Eddie Larran returns to Sparta for a concert, but not everyone is a fan. An angry man insists that Eddie owes him money. And their dispute soon ends in violence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210170000 +0000" stop="20241210180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Tailspin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob finds out he is not eligible to fly in the Air Corps due to bad vision</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210180000 +0000" stop="20241210190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Man's Buff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Phoebe nurses a wounded man with amnesia back to health. But with his memory returning it could lead to even more danger for the confused man and heartache for the lonely Phoebe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210190000 +0000" stop="20241210200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Lila Conrad Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe finds a saloon girl named Lila Conrad in the back of a wagon. Trouble is, she seems to be wanted—for murder. Joe wants to get her back to Virginia City for a fair trial, but it seems that other people have different plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210200000 +0000" stop="20241210203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Retired Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Wes Carney and his wife, Clair, want to settle down and they figure North Fork might do fine. Wes is a well known gunfighter, who has promised Clair that he would hang up his guns for good. The Carney's want to live a simple, honest life and the Feed and Grain Store, which is up for sale, seems like it might work for them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210203000 +0000" stop="20241210210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Photographer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Abel Goss, the photographer who took Lucas' wedding photograph, is in North Fork doing a portrait of Mark standing in the street. When Goss sees Col. Whiteside and his sidekick, Jamison, he recognizes them as the butchers who tortured him and others while he was captive in a Civil War prison camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210210000 +0000" stop="20241210220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Clementine Jones Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>"Clementine Jones is in the process of being thrown out of a town when a bank robbery occurs. She ends up joining the Hale wagon train on a wagon with one of the bank robbers using it to escape who she was in love with in the past."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210220000 +0000" stop="20241210230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Computer Error</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A young couple is rescued from a car wreck; the boy has a spinal cord injury and Dr. Early suspects the girl is pregnant. Roy and John rescue a woman trapped at the bottom of a well and an amateur magician from a safe. A rescue at a junkyard fire turns hazardous when phosphorus materials explode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210230000 +0000" stop="20241210233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Incubator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper recover from an all night party. Henry gets a barbecue, and Hawkeye puts in a request for an incubator. The Quartermaster turns him down. They locate a Major with three incubators, but he won't let them have one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210233000 +0000" stop="20241211000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Deal Me Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Sidney Freedman comes to the camp, and joins in the poker game at The Swamp. Radar hits a local with a jeep, although the local is famous for jumping in front of vehicles for the compensation. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on an intelligence officer against regulations, and Sidney helps talk a soldier out of his plan to kill Frank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211000000 +0000" stop="20241211003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips And Empty Arms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret revaluates her life, deciding to leave Frank and ask for a transfer, which is granted. She gets drunk at her goodbye party, but is sobered up in the shower when wounded start arriving. She changes her mind when she realizes how loyal her friends are.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211003000 +0000" stop="20241211010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Officers Only</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger pretends to be pregnant. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on General Mitchell's son, and the General gives them three days in Tokyo, and Henry keeps getting calls from Tokyo about what Hawkeye and Trapper are doing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211010000 +0000" stop="20241211013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's Vacation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A grumpy Andy agrees to take a few days off and heads up to the lake to relax. Barney and Gomer are in charge, and manage to capture (and lose) an escaped convict who hides in the same woods where Andy just happens to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211013000 +0000" stop="20241211020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is convinced that Andy saved his life by putting out a small fire at the filling station. He then begins to repay Andy by becoming his servant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211020000 +0000" stop="20241211023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Annul That Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After Shorty and Gloria get married, everyone but the two of them want the marriage annulled. Gloria decides she’d like to experience what her new life will be like, and Jed tells her that he’ll show her. When he calls the mansion to tell them to put up the cabin, Granny thinks he got married as well. But when both “couples” come home, Granny, Jethro, and Elly learn that Shorty got married, but Elverna didn’t, and Gloria got married, but Jed didn’t, making Jethro and Granny believe both couples are in a Hollywood marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211023000 +0000" stop="20241211030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Spring Festival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone in Hooterville, except Oliver, is overcome with spring fever; even Sam Drucker is wearing his spring toupee. Deciding to revive the Hooterville spring festival, Lisa visits the neighbors to drum up support. Meanwhile, Oliver tries to do his planting with Eb who can't understand how to work the automatic planter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211030000 +0000" stop="20241211033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Kommandant Dies At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink is to be executed when the Gestapo finds him with information Hogan planted on him to deliver to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211033000 +0000" stop="20241211040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Bombsight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get the blueprints for and interfere with the testing of a new weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211040000 +0000" stop="20241211043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Barby And Ben / Rancid Harvest</sub-title>
    <desc>In Barby and Ben, a toy couple's marriage is threatened by the arrival of a G.I. doll. Then, in Rancid and Harvest, a parody of "Random Harvest", with Carol as Greer Garson, a woman who falls for a man with no memory of his past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211043000 +0000" stop="20241211053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Moth-eaten Mink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Restaurateur Morey Allen, a friend of Mason and Della's, contacts Mason after his waitress, Dixie Dayton, is struck by a car while fleeing the restaurant after spotting a man stalking her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211053500 +0000" stop="20241211060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Odyssey Of Flight 33</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A commercial aircraft mysteriously travels back through time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211060500 +0000" stop="20241211063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Mink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A housewife buys a stolen mink for $400.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211063500 +0000" stop="20241211070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Decoy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Gil is in love with a married singer who wants to kill her abusive husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211070500 +0000" stop="20241211080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Upside Down Penny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix works a case involving a child's missing stamp album. It appears as though someone is more than willing to kill for it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211080500 +0000" stop="20241211090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Is A Double Cross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired to be a bodyguard for the daughter of a broker and his grandchildren, but is drawn in when the broker reveals that he believes his son in law is involved in a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211090500 +0000" stop="20241211100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A millionaire hires Barnaby to rescue his son from kidnappers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211100000 +0000" stop="20241211103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>License Plates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Matthews pursues a recidivist thief with a tip from a young boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211103000 +0000" stop="20241211110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Jobs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A nervy bank robber uses innocent women to help commit his crimes. Friday and Gannon are nearly sidetracked when one of the victims lies about her involvement and later proves to have a criminal record of her own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211110000 +0000" stop="20241211113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Routine Patrol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin today's patrol by responding to a call of a drunken woman threatening the patrons of a bar with a handgun. Afterwards, they search for a group of four carjackers who go on a robbery spree after targeting a man with a cache of guns in his trunk, and investigate the suspicious death of a mentally disabled man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211113000 +0000" stop="20241211120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Sunburn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed returns from vacation with a full-body sunburn, making for a miserable work day. Out on patrol, he and Malloy respond to a fiery traffic accident, use an informant's tip to track down a drug dealer, search for an armed robbery suspect based on a vehicle description and attempt to rescue two boys after their rowboat capsizes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211120000 +0000" stop="20241211130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Silver State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony embrace the extraordinariness of Nevada, from the glitz and glam of Vegas to alien encounters."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211130000 +0000" stop="20241211133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's First Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A party is being thrown at the dancing school where Beaver and Wally once took lessons and they're both invited. This prompts Beaver to ask one particular girl who caught his eye, Betsy Patterson, if he could escort her to the dance. However, once at the dance, he finds that Betsy has promised other boys that she would dance with them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211133000 +0000" stop="20241211140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Ward's Golf Clubs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>During a particularly awful golf game, Ward happens to break his driver and decides it's not worth repairing it, so he just puts it in the closet. Later, Gilbert talks Beaver into hitting around some golf balls with Ward's clubs and one hit with the broken driver has Beaver thinking he broke it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211140000 +0000" stop="20241211150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Red Riding Boots</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ann Farwell is miserable over the separation of her parents. Things aren't made any better when her father starts seeing Rita Conover, a scheming woman half his age. When Rita turns up dead both Ann and her mother think the other committed the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211150000 +0000" stop="20241211160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Scrooge  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a scrooge of a store owner is accused of murdering his partner, Matlock defends the man and makes a strange request as part of his fee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211160000 +0000" stop="20241211170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Blessings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>In this Christmas episode the officers share memories with a reporter from the Sparta Herald.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211170000 +0000" stop="20241211180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>Founder's Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The town prepares for a Founder's Day Celebration</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211180000 +0000" stop="20241211190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Alias Festus Haggen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus is mistaken for a killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211190000 +0000" stop="20241211200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Ponderosa Matador</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam, Hoss, and Joe vie for the attention of a pretty young lady named Dolores. Hoss talks Joe into entering a bull fight, but it doesn't work out quite as planned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211200000 +0000" stop="20241211203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shivaree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Aaron Pelser's wagon train comes across a pair of young boys on a buck board heading west, so he invites them to join the train. When he finds out that one of the boys is actually a girl and the two claim to be headed to Yuma to get married, Pelser and his crowd force them to be married in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211203000 +0000" stop="20241211210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadeye Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>McCain befriends Donnel O'Mahoney, a tough kid from Brooklyn, and arranges with two men for the young man to continue his travels on their wagon. Things go wrong, however, when one of them is murdered, and the other accuses the boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211210000 +0000" stop="20241211220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jenna Douglas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>"Jenna Douglas is found by scouts for the wagon train. She appears to have been a victim of a scavenger attack and is adopted by the train. As time goes on people on the train begin to have doubts about her story and her mental state."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211220000 +0000" stop="20241211230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Inferno</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy are disappointed when they are the only squad not called to a major brushfire. Dixie gets her hand caught in a vending machine. A lawyer collapses in the courtroom with an apparent heart attack. Roy and John finally make it to the brushfire and become trapped while rescuing another firefighter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211230000 +0000" stop="20241211233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry In Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry returns from a week in Tokyo, announcing that he is in love with a 20-year-old girl named Nancy Sue Parker. When she arrives for the weekend, it isn't long before she starts making advances on Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211233000 +0000" stop="20241212000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For Want Of A Boot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In this riotous episode, Hawkeye gets wrapped up in a convoluted scheme to procure a new pair of boots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212000000 +0000" stop="20241212003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Noselift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Private Baker, who is always going AWOL, is desperate for plastic surgery on his nose. Hawkeye gets an old friend, and plastic surgeon, to visit the camp, promising him a nurse called "The Barracuda." They put together an elaborate scheme to perform the operation without Frank or Margaret finding out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212003000 +0000" stop="20241212010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Chosen People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A Korean family sets up camp in the middle of the compound. A Korean woman with a baby comes looking for the father, and names Radar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212010000 +0000" stop="20241212013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bargain Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, in a flurry of cost-cutting measures, saves money on beef by buying a whole side of it. Unfortunately, this happens at the same time her freezer breaks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212013000 +0000" stop="20241212020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Divorce, Mountain Style</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy finds himself embroiled in a strange backwoods divorce ritual, ending up as the object of Charlene Darling's affections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212020000 +0000" stop="20241212023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Honest John Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro comes home to tell Jed that he saw Honest John, but never caught up to him. Meanwhile, Honest John tells his wife he's turned straight, but she gets mad and threatens him. She wants him to con the wealthy Clampetts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212023000 +0000" stop="20241212030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Our Son, The Barber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Eb's latest career choice is that of a barber. He talks Oliver into paying his tuition to MIT, a mail-order barber college. Eb's sent a dummy head and hair to practice on and receives his grades by mailing the trimmed toupees back to the school. Lisa is excited about Eb's education while Oliver is irritated by all the hidden costs he keeps being asked to pay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212030000 +0000" stop="20241212033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to steal the picture that the Gestapo is using to blackmailing Klink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212033000 +0000" stop="20241212040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gamble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must prevent the Germans from getting ahold of a secret device that was aboard a plane shot down near camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212040000 +0000" stop="20241212043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In George and Zelda, a disguised Carol and Harvey complain to the audience before the show. Then, in The Spy, a WWII bomber pilot jumps without a parachute. Finally, in The Ham Actor, a TV debut for an acting duo goes horribly wrong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212043000 +0000" stop="20241212053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Baited Hook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert Dawson confronts Albert Tydings, his partner, about $80,000 missing from Carol Stanley's trust account. Tydings admits he embezzled the money and blackmails Dawson into keeping quiet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212053500 +0000" stop="20241212060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Dingle, The Strong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Martians give Luther Dingle the strength of 300 men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212060500 +0000" stop="20241212063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Momentum</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>A man ends up running to the Mexican border after trying to collect money his employer owes him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212063500 +0000" stop="20241212070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Wet Saturday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A vulnerable man is pinned with a murder he did not commit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212070500 +0000" stop="20241212080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>One Step To Midnight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to protect the granddaughter of an exiled mobster. It seems as though she's being stalked by hoods who want to get to her grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212080500 +0000" stop="20241212090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Nowhere Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An accountant wants to teach the world a lesson about the production of a deadly nerve gas when he steals a can of the substance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212090500 +0000" stop="20241212100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Frame For Murder, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>J.R. attempts to save his reputation when he's framed for rape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212100000 +0000" stop="20241212103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Hitchhiker Dies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A hitchhiker implicates a man who gave him a ride.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
